第一天
上午8：30
第二天
凌晨4：45
第三天
上午9：15
35岁退休
第一季第1集
－＝维他命工作室 倾情奉献＝－
本字幕仅供学习交流之用 严禁用于商业用途
翻译：世界
校对：西西
精校：jjooyy
后期：IDM
---------------------------------
维他命工作室    荣誉出品
我知道你是我老板
Donald, Donald I know you're my boss, ok?
我知道
I know... well
但是你在嘶吼 Donald 真刺耳啊
But you're yelling, Donald, and it's hurting my ears.
Donald 很高兴知道我很有价值 我...
Donald, I'm glad I'm valuable. I'm--
但是我现在不能立刻回纽约
But I can't come back to New York right now.
因为我已经在佛罗里达给老妈过生日了
Well, because I'm already in Florida for my mom's birthday
而且...
And...
听着Donald 整个周末我手机都不离身
Listen, Donald, I will have my phone with me all weekend.
我保证
I promise.
现在我要进去了
Uh, so I'm going in now,
你可以一个小时后给我打电话 行吧
Uh, but you can call me in an hour, okay?
一个小时
One hour. Okay.
哦 Donald 还没到一小时呢
Well, that wasn't an hour, donald.
对不起 但是我现在已经在我父母家门口了
Listen, I'm sorry, but I'm at my parents' door now,
他们还认为手机辐射对人体有害
And they still think that cell phones have harmful rays.
- 我待会给你打回去 - 你回来啦
-I will call you back. -There he is!
我的David回来了
My David is here.
爸妈 你们看上去很健康啊
Mom, dad! You guys look great.
你会喜欢这儿的
You're gonna love it here.
就像慢镜头的大学生活
It's like college in slow motion.
- 我...我是Richard 你爹的朋友
- I'm--I'm Richard, your dad's friend.
他老是提起你
He talks about you constantly.
弄得我总觉得我儿子是窝囊废
Kinda makes me feel like my son is a loser.
实际上他还真是
Which he is.
- 快进来
- Come on in.
你能别鼓弄那破手机吗
Will you stop with all the texturizing?
- 不是 我们有规定的
- No, no, we have rules.
不准打手机 不准系领带
No cell phones, no ties,
两个月后 寡妇们就手到擒来了
And after two months, widows are fair game.
- 把电话给我
- Give me the phone.
- 爸 我不能把电话给你
- Oh, dad, I can't give you my phone.
对不起 工作上有个大项目
I'm sorry. We've got a big project at work,
我老板就指望我了
And my boss is just all over me.
- 大项目 你不是做筷子的吗
- Big project? Don't you make chopsticks?
是 也做牙签和雪糕棍
Yes. Also toothpicks and popsicle sticks,
所有与食物有关的木头啊
Really all food-related wood.
- Amy Amy 看 是David
- Amy. Amy, look, it's David.
给David拿点葡萄 他累啊
Will you get david some grapes? He's tired.
- 我完蛋了
- And we're off.
Amy 给David拿点葡萄
"Amy, get david some grapes.
Amy 给David洗衣服 活在David的阴影中吧
Amy, do david's laundry. Amy, live in david's shadow."
- Amy现在有男盆友了
- Amy has a boyfriend now.
- 男盆友 真的
- Wow, a boyfriend. Amy, really?
- 哦 是的 这回他是真实存在的
- Uh, yeah. And this time, he exists.
- David 你到得刚刚好
- David, you got here just in time
我刚要来个即兴艺术展
For my impromptu art show.
- 你妈的画 -画 真的
- Your mother's painting now. - Painting? Really?
- 是的 真能让人释放压力啊 - 压力 什么压力
- Oh, yes. It relieves stress. - Stress? What stress?
- 有鸭梨啊
- Oh, there's stress.
我活了一生
You know, I spent my whole life
就等着能陪你爹
Waiting to spend time with your father,
现在我所剩的就是和你爹待在一起
And now all I have is time with your father.
你小时候我就描描画画的
You know, I used to sketch things when you were young,
- 但是怀了Amy  - 出乎预料的Amy 是我
- But once Amy came along... - Unexpected amy, that's me.
- 别那么说 你是我们熬过
- Oh, stop. You were a wonderful surprise
激情殆尽期的美好惊喜啊
Once we got over the initial shock.
- David 看
- David, look.
我不明白为啥她就不能画一碗水果
I don't know why she can't just paint a nice bowl of fruit.
那也算得上水果啊
She kinda did.
- 他叫Manu
- His name is Manu.
Manu住在葡萄牙
Manu lives in Portugal.
他是搓澡工兼洗碗工
He gives back rubs and empties the dishwasher.
- David 别管它
- David, let it go.
- 爸 我整个人都在你这
- Dad, I am totally with you.
我就是有很多事要做
I just have a lot of balls in the air.
但是 妈 你不要画它们（ball有蛋的意思）
Don't go painting them, though, mom.
- 哦不会的
- Oh, I won't.
我永远都不会屈服的
Took me forever to get these right.
- 看你这样过度工作真让我伤心啊
- Breaks my heart to see you overworked like this.
你应该多去健身房
You need to get to the gym more.
看看这小鸡胳膊
Look at this little chicken arm here.
我打赌我掰手腕能赢你
I bet I could beat you at arm wrestling.
来吧 我赢了 你把手机给我
Come on. I win, I get your cell phone.
- 好了 大家 开战了
- All right, everybody, here we go.
围起来 就要上演掰手腕大赛
Gather round. Arm-wrestling match right over here.
快点 坐下
Come on. Sit down. Come on.
开战 开战 开战...
Fight! Fight! Fight! Fight!
- 抽死他 爸爸 把他那小胳膊掰断
- Whip him, dad! Snap that little chicken arm.
- 你老爸掰手腕赢你了
- Your old man whipped you at arm wrestling?
说真的 老兄 雄起啊
Seriously, man, do a curl.
我应该和他们掰拇指的
I should thumb wrestle them.
我已从发短信中练就拇指神功
My thumb are huge form texting
- 哥们 我就不该来这儿
- Man, I never should have come down here.
我没办法让每个人都高兴
There's just no way I can keep everyone happy.
- 哥们 那就是
- That, my friend,
为啥我对让别人失望毫不在意
Is why I'm comfortable disappointing everyone.
人们总是对我说
See, people say to me all the time,
Brandon 你最好的朋友David去纽约了
"Brandon, your best pal david went off to new york
出人头地了
"And made something of himself,
而你就在家扫泳池
"And you're just a pool man in your hometown.
你不觉得窝囊吗
Doesn't that make you feel like a loser?"
我就对他们说 爸妈 不
And I say to those people, "No, mom and dad, it doesn't."
- 天那 是Jessica Sanders吗
- Oh, my gosh. Is that jessica sanders?
- 是 她在这工作
- Yeah, she works here.
- 这 在这酒吧
- Here? In this bar?
上帝啊 我过去很迷她啊
God, I was crazy about her.
是吗 她现在想要我
Yeah, well, she wants me now.
- 神马 - 你离开这去纽约
- What? - Well, you're off in new york
享受着光鲜的工作和辣妹
With the big job and hot girlfriend.
我就是那么勾搭上Jessica的 我拿你吹牛
That's how I hit on jessica-- I brag about you.
- 我和女朋友分手了
- Well, my girlfriend and I broke up.
她背着我和维修工偷情
She cheated on me with the maintenance man.
- 这部分就拉倒吧
- Leave that part out.
我们是高中同学
We went to high school together.
- 是吗 - 是
- Did we? - Yeah.
- 在高中
- In high school,
在他的衣柜里有你的神像
He had a shrine built to you in his closet.
- 不是神像啦
- It wasn't a shrine.
就是个拼图而已
It was more of a collage.
- David 最近怎么样啊
- David, how have you been?
上次听说你的时候 你是个大人物
Last I heard, you were, like, some big shot
现在住在纽约
Living in new york now.
- 不
- Oh, no.
嗯 不好说
Well, yeah, you know, I don't know.
不清楚啊 过的还可以
I don't know, you know, things are good.
来这...待几天拜访下大家
Just, uh, down here visiting the folks for a few days.
但是 工作不错
But, uh, career's great.
我女朋友原来是个卖的
Uh, my girlfriend turned out to be a whore.
我又单身了 那很好
So--so I'm single, so that's good.
我不是说她真是个卖的
Yeah. And I don't mean a literal whore,
不是那种老鸨带着卖淫的妓女
Not a hooker, whore with a pimp.
不是 不是
That's not--no.
她睡了维修工
She slept with the maintenance man.
原来洗碗机能制造出好玩的声音
But it turns out that the reason the washing machine
是因为他在它上面搞了我女朋友
Was making a funny sound is he was banging my girlfriend on it.
你过的咋样
How are you?
- 生活 工作 玩乐队
- Living, working, playing in a band.
- 那个挺酷的啊
- Oh, hey, that's cool, yeah.
我也去在乐队里面
I used to be in a band.
不是乐队
Not a band.
伙计帮
Band.
你在伙计帮待过
You were in band.
- 纽约听起来是挺有趣的
- Well, new york certainly sounds interesting.
给我打打电话
So why don't you give me a call
多告诉我点纽约的生活
And, you know, tell me more about it?
- 这和她给我的不一样
- This is different than the one she gave me.
- 老爸
- Hey, dad.
- 你上Facialbook吗(Facebooko)
- Are you on facial book?
- 不 老爸 我上titter(Twitter -_-!)
- No, dad, I'm tittering.
无线网的密码是啥
Uh, what is the wireless password?
- 没无线网
- No wireless.
- 别提了
- Got rid of it.
有些人禁受不住那些黄网对的诱惑
Those dirty websites were too tempting for some people.
- 黄片对我来说就像篮球
- Porn is like basketball to me.
我喜欢看别人做我过去做的事
I like watching people do things I used to do.
- 要是你戒烟了
- If you'd stop with the cigars,
说不定还能嘿咻下
Maybe you'd get some action.
- 嘿咻暗示激情和活塞运动
- Action implies enthusiasm and movement.
- 吃你的三明治吧
- Eat your sandwich.
- 木有熏肉啊
- There's no bacon.
- 我给你拿了黄豆熏肉
- I got you the soy bacon.
- 我不喜欢假肉(Fake)
- I don't like "Facon."
- 我也是 但是你不得不做你要做的（暗指假jj）
- Neither do I, but you do what you have to do.
- 快点 David 把手机放下
- Come on, david. Put that thing down
过来和我一起玩一天
And come spend the day with me.
有个大的棒球赛
We have a big softball game.
- 对不起老爸 待会出去行吗
- Ah, sorry, dad. Can we hang out later?
- 当然  -谢谢
- Sure. - Thanks.
- 现在行吗
- How about now?
- 爸爸 - 再不说了
- Dad. - Not another word.
我能看吗
Can I share?
我知道你很尽心尽力的工作
I know what you're going through with this work thing.
但是身体要紧啊 工作永不停息 没个尽头啊
Be careful. It never stops. There's no end to it.
这些人用钱把你梦想买了
These people pay you to give up your dreams.
上帝 我错过了你那么多比赛
God, I missed so many of your little-league games.
我在技术很烂的
I sucked at little league.
你还记得那次选拔吗
Don't your remember the draft?
只有俩个人
It was down to two players.
我和坐轮椅的Todd
It was me and wheelchair todd,
他们选了Todd 爸爸
And they picked todd, dad.
- 我罪孽深重啊
- Don't let me off the hook.
你知道我会用什么来换取
Do you know what I would give
让时光倒转 看你在赛场上奔跑
To go back to that time and see you out there on that field,
如鳟鱼那样遨游
Flailing around like a trout?
我宁愿放弃一切
I would give everything.
- 也行以后我们去抓点鳟鱼
- Maybe we can play some catch later.
- 以后以后 什么事都以后
- Later, later-- everything's later.
现在 现在就出去玩
Now--we play now.
- 老爸别这样 你把我电话当人质
- Oh, come on, dad. You're holding my phone hostage.
- 现在人质在我手里
- We have a hostage situation.
- 电话给我 给我 爸爸
- Give me the phone. Give me the phone. Dad.
- 和我去打球
- Play ball with me,
我保证我一定选你
And I promise I won't pick you last.
- 你保证过了 - 好吧
- You promised. - Fine.
我选David
I pick david.
- 妈 妈 我们赢了
- Mom, mom, we won.
我跑垒得了五分
Yeah, I scored five runs,
而且我扔了几个快要到一垒的球了
And I threw several balls almost all the way to first.
- 我真为他骄傲
- I'm so proud of him.
他亮了
He lightened up.
- 这真是我第一次获得奖杯啊
- And I won my very first trophy ever.
是金色的马桶垫
It is a gold, padded toilet seat,
灰常酷喔
And it is way cool.
- 你一定是David
- You must be david.
- 我是
- I am.
是 妈 你雇了个服务员
Yeah, ma, you hired a caterer?
- 没 傻子 我是Paul Amy的男朋友
- No, silly, I'm paul, amy's boyfriend.
见到你很高兴啊
So nice to meet you.
Amy过来帮我
oh, ames, come help me.
我在蛋黄酱上整点奶皮
I'm getting a skin on my bearnaise.
- 那是我男人
- That's my man.
- 妈 爸 你们不觉得Paul有点
- Mom, dad, does paul seem a little...
我不知道咋说
I don't know...
完全是同性恋
Completely gay to you?
- 只要他爱Amy给我们生孙子就行
- As long as he loves her and gives me a grandchild,
他在他自己的时间做他的事我管不着
What he does on his own time is his business.
- David 都2010年代了
- David, it's 2010.
谁还想和大男子汉约会
Who wants to date some big, macho guy?
- 可以确定的是Paul会 老爸
- Pretty sure paul does, dad.
- 这是一个美好的生日
- This has been a wonderful birthday,
你们都在身边 特别是你David
Having all of you here, especially you, david.
- 我听到了
- I heard that.
- 这次我突然回来
- I'm having a blast down here.
是这么长时间以来第一次 我能放松
For the first time in a long time, I am relaxed.
可以深呼吸 下巴不用绷紧
I'm breathing. My jaws are unclenched.
- 我随便做了点蛋糕
- I made upside-down cake.
我妈的秘方 但是少了她的坏脾气
My mother's recipe, but without the anger.
- 好吧 大伙现在开始给我唱歌吧
- Okay, everyone, you can sing to me now.
- 不好意思 继续
- Sorry. Go ahead.
- 不好意思 最后一次
- Sorry. Last time.
- 接电话
- Answer the phone.
- 好好 我会快点的
- All right, all right, I'll be quick.
好的 我...我去拿个笔
Yeah, okay, um, I-- let me just get a pen.
让...
Uh, let...
好吧 说吧
Um, okay, shoot.
记下了
Uh-huh. Uh-huh. Okay. Got it.
好的 不 事实上 Donald 不 你能慢点吗
Right, no, actually, donald, no, can you slow down?
- 你太快了  - 他在咬牙
-You're going too fast. - He's clenching.
- 他脖子绷紧了 - 他在毁了你的生日
- His neck's all tense. - He's ruining your birthday.
- 我能等会给你打回去吗
- Can I call you back?
只是 我们正好在庆祝我妈的生日
It's just--we're right in the middle of my mom's birthday,
所有的蜡烛都点着了
And the candles are lit,
我一分钟后就给你打回去 好吧
And I just need to call you back in--in one minute, okay?
Donald 我一分钟后就给你打回去
Donald, I'll just call you back in one minute.
Donald 我就一分钟后就给你回电话
Donald, I'll call you back in just a minute.
哦 55秒了Donald
Well, it's 55 seconds now, donald.
别浪费时间了
We're wasting time.
Donald 我等会给你打回去 行吗
Donald, I just want to call you back, okay?
让我等会给你回电话吧
Just please let me call you back?
我们卖食物相关的木头
We sell food-related wood.
Donald 那啥也不是
It means nothing, donald.
那个
It's...
知道吗 我再也不干了
You know what? I'm not doing this anymore.
不不不不 就现在
No, no, not just for now--
永远
Forever.
我辞职了
I quit.
- 你真的辞职了
- Hey, are you really quitting your job?
- 是的
- Yes.
在那儿真是痛苦
I am miserable up there.
老爸 我不想某一天有什么遗憾
I don't want to get to a certain age, dad, and have any regrets.
- 会有遗憾的
- There'll be regrets.
- David 真鼓舞人心啊
- Wow, david, this is very inspiring.
人们可以改变生活
A person can change their life.
我真为你高兴
I am so happy for you.
- 谢谢 老妈
- Thanks, mom.
- 至于我 你知道吗
- And for me, because you know what?
我也要改变的东西
I'm going to change something too.
- Allen 我要离开你
- Allen, I'm leaving you.
我要去葡萄牙画画
I'm going to portugal to paint.
我做了饼干 如果谁喜欢的话就吃吧
Oh, I made cookies, if anybody wants them.
- 我不能吃 屁股会发胖的
- I can't. They go right to my hips.
你妈真走了
Your mother's really gone.
- 是啊
- Yeah.
是 哦...
Yeah, um...
老爹 你还好吗
Dad, are you okay?
她走了 走了......
Oh, yeah, she's gone, gone, gone Oh, yeah, she's gone, gone, gone
- 她走了走了...... -好的好的好的
- She's gone, gone, gone Oh, yeah, she's gone, gone, gone -Okay, okay. Okay.
老爸 我知道这是你
Yeah, so, dad, I know this is your first
有点爵士风格的第一反应
Sort of dixieland reaction,
但是也许妈妈几个星期就回来了
Uh, but maybe mom will come back in a few weeks.
- 千万别这么说 - 神马
- Don't even say that. - What?
- 我以为你们以前很幸福 - 现在幸福了
- I thought you guys were happy. - We are now.
David 人们发明婚姻时
David, when marriage was invented,
寿命只有37岁
The life expectancy was 37.
结婚了 就能过上几天好日子
You were married, you had a few good years,
然后就被怪兽吃掉
And then you got eaten by some sort of wild beast.
- 什么
- What?
- 我们迈出一大步
- David, we had a great run.
你应该为你妈妈高兴
You should be happy for your mother.
她会做她想做的
She's gonna do what she wants to do,
我要做我想做的事
And I'm gonna do what I want.
- 我刚刚拆散了我父母
- Did I just break up my parents?
- 因为你 孩子 我们无数次的
- We almost broke up a whole bunch of times
徘徊的分手边缘了
Because of you kids.
这次终于分了而已
This time it stuck.
快点
Come on.
和我一起唱
Get into it.
你能再做点熏肉吗
Can you make me some more bacon?
- 爸 你难道不应该吃点除了熏肉以外的东西
- Dad, shouldn't you have something besides bacon?
- 你是啥 我老婆 快给我上熏肉
- What are you, my wife? Bacon me.
起来闪光吧
Rise and shine.
我在重新考虑熏肉
I'm rethinking the bacon.
- 我一直在想点事 - 神马
- I've been thinking about something. - Yeah?
你认为我自己用五弦琴把自己
How long do you think it would take me
打死得花多长时间
to beat myself to death with a banjo?
- 劳驾 Jessica
- Excuse me, Jessica.
我们要60个鸡翅膀
Could we get 60 chicken wings
再来几瓶啤酒
And a couple pitchers of beer?
你想要点啥
You want anything?
- David 我很奇怪
- So, david, I've been kind of wondering,
你是不是把我电话号码丢掉了
Did you lose my number?
- 木有
- No.
为啥 你这样说是...
Why, did you tell me to?
- 没
- No.
- 对不起啊
- I'm sorry.
只是这周末有点疯狂
It's just been kind of a crazy week.
我辞职了然后和我爸结婚了
Turns out I quit my job and married my dad.
- 你知道吗 我改变想法了
- You know what? I changed my mind.
我想要点沙拉
I'll have the salad.
但是还是要啤酒
Still bring the beer, though.
要一步一步来
Gonna do this in steps.
- Brandon 我刚才是对David说的
- You know, brandon, I was talking to david.
- 对不起 我就觉得咱俩有共同之处
- Sorry, I just thought you and I had something in common.
你是领养的 我父母告诉他们朋友说我是领养的
You're adopted, my parents tell their friends I'm adopted.
- 我们就这么点共同点
- That's our connection?
是共同的东西
it's something.
- 也许你老爸有点想你妈了
- Maybe your dad just misses your mom a little bit.
这儿有好多女人可供选择
There are tons of available women down here.
- 是啊
- Yes.
我们得给你爸爸找个对象
We got to find your dad a date.
- 我不知道啊
- Oh, I don't know, guys.
我不知道怎样给他找对象
I mean, how are we gonna find him a date?
- 有了
- Bingo.
- 你知道谁吗
- What, you know somebody?
- 不 是娱乐城
- No, bingo.
别担心了 什么都会好起来的
Don't worry, everything's gonna be fine.
我们会给他找个对象 我们会帮他走出来的
We'll get your dad a date, we'll get him back out there,
也许我还能收集点选票
And maybe I can collect some of the runoff.
- 我不知道 老兄
- I don't know, man.
感觉很奇怪啊
I just feel weird, you know?
我能想到的就是我妈
All I can think about is my mom.
- 我看了你妈画了啥
- I saw what your mom was painting.
相信我 她会没事的
Trust me, she's gonna be fine.
那就有一个
There's one now.
- 掩护我 我去和她谈谈
- Cover me, goose, I'm going in.
不要慌张 我是Brandon
Don't panic. I'm brandon.
我打扫泳池
I clean pools.
- 好
- All right.
- 最近我遇到个很棒的单身男人
- So recently I met an awesome and available man.
- 恭喜啊
- Congratulations.
- 给你的 给你的男人
- For you--a man for you.
- 那么这个人是谁啊
- So who is this awesome and available man?
- 他是那个家伙更老更帅
- He's an older, better-looking,
更强壮的版本
And stronger version of that kid right there.
他玩五弦琴
And he plays the banjo.
- 要是那样的话 我把那琴吃了都行
- For the right man, I can stomach the banjo.
- 就按你那么说定了
- Well, there you go. It's a date.
- 好极了 - B-9
- Great. - B-9
你还真画了个
Hey, you got one there.
B-9 听起来像个肿瘤似的(benign有良性的意思)
B-9, like the tumor.
良性的没啥 对吧
Hey, benign is the good kind, right?
- 好啊 邻居
- Hey, neighbor.
- 好 伙计
- Hey, dickie.
- 看起来不错
- Oh, looking good.
我听说你今晚有个盛大的约会啊
I-I heard somebody has a big date tonight,
所以我给你带了个小礼物
So I brought you a little present--
西力士（壮阳药）和医用大麻
Cialis and medical marijuana.
我管它叫烟袋和钱袋
I call it "A toke and a poke."
- 老爸 时间到了该去约会了
- Okay, dad, time to get ready for your big date.
给你找了个对象
Gonna get you out on a date.
- 一起看看是什么货色
- Shall we, uh, take a peek at the goods?
- 真激动啊
- This is exciting.
- 太老了 - 太老了
- Too old. - Too old.
- 太老了 什么 老爸 你疯了
- Too old? What? Dad, are you out of your mind?
她是娱乐城最性感的女的了
She was the hottest woman at bingo.
- 娱乐城
- Bingo?
不要 那些女人传瞎话
No, those women talk.
- 他有一头好头发 晚上能开车
- He's got a nice head of hair, and he can drive at night.
在这 这就是档次 A等肉
Down here, that's grade-a beef.
- 我如果和她约会
- If I date that woman,
我就会像Dean Martin一样被围观
I'll be hounded like dean martin.
- David 你还在吗
- David, are you still there?
我都不知道他都在想啥
I have no idea of what he was thinking.
根本没在想东西
He wasn't thinking.
- David 有什么问题吗
- David, is there a problem?
- 哦...有点小问题
- Um, just-- little, tiny problem.
不是大问题
Uh, not a big problem--
小问题 有趣的问题
Little problem, fun-size problem.
我老爸有恐慌症
Um, my--my dad is agoraphobic.
他害怕出去
Yeah, he's afraid to go outside.
- 他现在偷偷溜出去了 是吧
- He's sneaking out the back right now, isn't he?
- 是的
- Yes.
- 都他妹的一样 这儿的男人
- Ugh, it's all the same, these men down here.
一旦他们有对象了
Once they become available,
还真以为是怪人Dean Martin了
They all think they're dean frickin' martin.
- 不是 知道吗
- Hey, no, no, you know what?
不是你的问题 不是
It's not you. No, no, I mean, y--
你很有吸引力 热辣
Look, you are attractive and sexy,
他们应该羞耻
And they should be ashamed of themselves.
- 我都穿这样了 我准备好去吃饭了
- Well, I'm all dressed up and ready to go to dinner.
你想带我去吃饭吗
Do you want to maybe take me out for a bite to eat?
- 当然 我愿意啊
- Well, of course I would. Yeah.
只是现在才四点半
I mean, it's only 4:30.
但是我就说是比较晚的午饭
But you know what? I'll just call it a late lunch.
- 能现弄点喝的吗
- Can we have a drink first?
- 咕噜噜 喜欢喝东西
- Glug, glug. Love a drink, yeah.
- 谢谢
- Thank you so much.
- 不客气
- You're welcome.
知道吗 你应该约她出去
You know what? You should start dating her.
不用三块钱她就能入角色
She gets in the movies for 3 dollars less.
- 那女的咋样
- How was that woman?
她不高兴了
Was she upset?
- 是有一会不高兴
- Well, for a minute, she was.
然后David就让她飘然了
Then david made her feel all better.
- David 我刚才看错她了
- David, I was wrong about her.
她一点也不老
She's not too old at all.
- 他慌神了 这人慌神了
- He panicked. The man panicked.
他都结婚那么长时间了
He's been married for so long,
他都不知道咋要求嘿咻了
How would he even broach the subject of lovemaking?
- 我该说啥
- Yeah, what would I say?
如果现在你不是太累 我们就可以开始干了
"I'd like to have sex now if you're not too tired?"
我就知道这些
I mean, that's all I know.
谁都知道这点儿
That's all any of us know.
- 能给我她电话号码吗
- Could I get her phone number?
- David给他电话号码
- Give him the number, david.
- 不是个好主意
- That's a bad idea.
她真的真的很疯狂（生气）
She was really, really mad.
- 是的 她又喊又叫的
- Yeah, she was yelling and screaming
用她手指甲往死里扣他的背
And digging her nails into his back.
- 真是对不起啊
- Well, I'm so sorry.
我请你喝啤酒吧
Let me buy you a beer.
我们说是比较晚的午饭
We'll call it a late lunch.
David和娱乐城的女的上床了
David got laid by the bingo lady
- David上床了... - 打住 能打住吗
- David got laid - Stop it. Will you stop it?
- David 多幸运啊
- David! What luck.
看看我找到谁了 是Susan
Look who I found. It's susan.
- 你好啊
- How are you?
- 她一点也不生我的气
- She's not mad at me at all.
我不知道你对她说啥了 还真管用啊
I don't know what you said to her, but it really worked.
- 他很蛋定
- He's very calming.
- 天啊 你好 - 天啊 你好
- Oh, my gosh. Hi. - Oh, my god. Hi.
- 看看你认识我妈妈了
- Oh, I see you met my mom.
- 中彩了
- Bingo.